<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>My Ecommerce</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/</link>
	<description>Project</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 06:26:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/LogoMakr-6xurIF-100x100.png</url>
	<title>My Ecommerce</title>
	<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Betsy DeVos Resigns Over Trump Involvement in U.S. Capitol Riot</title>
		<link>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/betsy-devos-resigns-over-trump-involvement-in-u-s-capitol-riot/</link>
					<comments>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/betsy-devos-resigns-over-trump-involvement-in-u-s-capitol-riot/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[newaz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US Election]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/?p=138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[EDUCATION SECRETARY Betsy Devos has resigned, effective Friday – the second of Trump&#8217;s Cabinet members to do so just one day after mobs of pro-Trump supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol as Congress was formally recognizing Joe Biden&#8217;s victory in the presidential race. &#8220;There is no mistaking the impact your rhetoric had on the situation, and it [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p><span class="lede">EDUCATION SECRETARY </span>Betsy Devos has resigned, effective Friday – the second of Trump&#8217;s Cabinet members to do so just one day after mobs of pro-Trump supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol as Congress was formally recognizing Joe Biden&#8217;s victory in the presidential race.</p>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>&#8220;There is no mistaking the impact your rhetoric had on the situation, and it is the inflection point for me,&#8221; DeVos, one of the longest-serving members of the president&#8217;s Cabinet, said in a letter obtained by U.S. News and first reported by The Wall Street Journal.</p>
</div>
<div id="ac-lre-player-ph">
<div id="ac-lre-player"></div>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>&#8220;Impressionable children are watching all of this, and they are learning from us,&#8221; she said in the letter. &#8220;I believe we each have a moral obligation to exercise good judgment and model the behavior we hope they would emulate. They must know from us that America is greater than what transpired yesterday.&#8221;</p>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>DeVos was one of the only sitting Cabinet members to make a forceful statement against the violence Wednesday, albeit one that fell short of implicating the president.</p>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>&#8220;The eyes of America&#8217;s children and students – the rising generation who will inherit the republic we leave them – are watching what is unfolding in Washington today,&#8221; she said in a statement Wednesday. &#8220;We must set a better example for them, and we must teach them the solemn obligations and duties that come with the title &#8216;American.&#8217; The peaceful transfer of power is what separates American representative democracy from banana republics.&#8221;</p>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>She continued: &#8220;An angry mob cannot be allowed to attack our Capitol and indeed this process. The disruptions and violence must end, the law must be applied, and the work of the people must go on.&#8221;</p>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>The announcement comes as members of Congress in the House and Senate, including at least one Republican, as well as governors from both sides of the aisle and major business organizations, push to impeach the president and pressure Vice President Mike Pence to invoke the 25th Amendment to remove Trump from office immediately.</p>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>Invoking the 25th Amendment requires Pence and a majority of the sitting Cabinet members – as well as a two-thirds supermajority from the House and Senate if the president were to object – to seize executive power. The resignation of Devos, along with that of Transportation Secretary Elaine Chao, who is married to Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, drew criticism from many who characterized the departures as taking an easy escape hatch to shield them from a potentially damaging vote in support of or against removing the president from the executive office.</p>
</div>
<div class="Raw-slyvem-0 jsKuwX">
<p>Other less senior White House officials also resigned in the wake of Wednesday&#8217;s events, including Mick Mulvaney, special U.S. envoy to Northern Ireland and former Trump chief of staff; Sarah Matthews, the White House deputy press secretary; Matthew Pottinger, deputy national secretary adviser; Tyler Godspeed, chairman of the president&#8217;s Council of Economic Advisers; Anna Cristina Niceta, White House social secretary; Stephanie Grisham, chief of staff for first lady Melania Trump; and John Costello, deputy assistant secretary at the Commerce Department.</p>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mdshanewaz.github.io/WordPress-Proj-1/betsy-devos-resigns-over-trump-involvement-in-u-s-capitol-riot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
